KISHAN CHOUDHARY



in.kishanchoudhary@gmail.com



**** 7877641965



linkedin.com/in/kishan-choudhary-9390a1146

Summary

An individual with 4+ years of experience in Android Development. Career goal is to become a fully-qualified and experience software's developer, with long-term aspiration of moving into engineering management. I remain flexible with time and dedicated with on time deliveries. Focus on growth and new learnings.

Experience



Android Developer

ARKA Softwares

Dec 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

Worked with new technologies like Clean Architecture (MVVM), Hilt, Navigation

components, Coroutines, Room DB, Google MLKit, Razor pay, Cashfree.

Worked on project like e-commerce mobile app and booking doctor appointment

Cricket fantasy app like Vijayi Bhawa, E-Learning platform that offer offline content and test series with student report card.

Projects: Vijayi Bhawa, MsingiPack, Spitar App, JabyJob, AlamalhaFlat



👗 Android Developer

EzyTm Technologies

Oct 2020 - Nov 2021 (1 year 2 months)

Mobile Recharge-

Mobile & DTH recharge.

Utility bill payments.

Buy & manage fastag.

AEPS - morpho & mantra device.

Project: Recharge Duniya Services

Worked on micro ATM.



Android App Developer

VolanSoft Technologies Private Limited

Nov 2018 - Sep 2020 (1 year 11 months)

SellAMoon is an app-based platform for buying and selling pre owned items, be it new or old with supporting services. Developed a unique and simple 3 step

posting process which makes posting ads fast, smooth and simple. Developed in Java.

Social Login, Firebase, Crash Analytics

Project SellaMoon

This is encompassing nevertheless a thorough going wedding search portal.

Firebase, Onesignal

Project: AmritLife

It helps you order your favorite homemade meal whenever and wherever you

need it and even get it delivered to your door. Just order by going through the list of food items on this IOS Bhozn App. Developed in java.

Social Login ,Firebase, Crash Analytics

Project :- Bhozn Guest

This is a food ordering app. Just order by going through the list of food items on this IOS Bhozn App.

Developed in Java.

Firebase, Crash Analytics

Project: **Bhozn Chef**

Single handedly manage and develop online Matka Applications (Number Bidding)

Owned features like Add, Deposit money using Razor pay

Social login, Firebase, Crash Analytics Projects: DreamStarLine, **Tiger Matka**

Education



Maharishi Arvind Institute of Engineering & Technology, Jaipur

Bachelor of Computer Application 2013 - 2016



JECRC University

Master of Computer Applications, Computer Science 2016 - 2018

Skills

```
Android Studio · Android SDK · Java · Kotlin · Basecamp · Zeplin · Git · Bitbucket · Dependency Injection · Debugging · Room Database · Debugging Jetpack Compose · MVVM
```

Honors & Awards



Employee of the month - VolanSoft Technologies Private Limited

Nov 2019